Contact

mckskwiera@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mskwierawski (LinkedIn) skwiera-magic.github.io/portfolio/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

JavaScript HTML5 GitHub

Languages

polski (Native or Bilingual) angielski (Full Professional) hiszpański (Elementary)

Certifications

CompTIA A+ 220-1001(Core 1)
CompTIA A+ 220-1002(Core 2)
It Fundamentals

Maciej Skwierawski

Call Centre agent

Greater Liverpool Area

Summary

After working number of years in warehouses and factories I decided that I don't like safety shoes anymore. So I changed work to call centre. After about 2 years I understood that I don't like direct contact with customers so now I am working to move to IT.

Experience

Capita

Call Center Agent May 2022 - February 2023 (10 months)

Liverpool, England, United Kingdom

Kura (CS) Ltd
Call Center Agent
April 2021 - May 2022 (1 year 2 months)
Liverpool, England, United Kingdom

ODL, Inc FLT Driver July 2020 - February 2021 (8 months) Bootle, Anglia, Wielka Brytania

First 3 months as blinds builder Rest as FLT Driver

IAC Group FLT Driver July 2019 - July 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Halewood, Anglia, Zjednoczone Królestwo Wielkiej Brytanii

Working as holiday cover, most time (60%)on FLT truck, rest on the production line as QC or operative

Serco
Agent call center
December 2018 - July 2019 (8 months)

Liverpool, Anglia, Zjednoczone Królestwo Wielkiej Brytanii

Providing support during first step of government support application

IAC Group

FLT Driver

July 2018 - December 2018 (6 months)

Halewood, Anglia, Zjednoczone Królestwo Wielkiej Brytanii

Loading/unloading wagons, managing stock in the warehouse, supplying production line.

Comau

FLT Driver

February 2018 - July 2018 (6 months)

Halewood, Anglia, Zjednoczone Królestwo Wielkiej Brytanii

Moving construction materials and production line robots during renovation in Jaguar Land Rover factory

Education

edX

Certificate, Front-end Web Developer \cdot (November 2022 - March 2023)